Ernest L. Hartmann Papers MS211
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Research data and materials, 1900 -- 2014; MS211.005; 67.2 Linear Feet
  MS211-004: 'BQ small SPSS programs from BC vax' [original title]. The original is the first of two floppy disks found in folder "BQ-BC data-2000." These disks were found in an envelope wrapped in a letter from Rani E. Dalgin of Boston College (which remains in the folder). This disk contains many different file extensions including .SPPS, .OLD, and .LIS data files. The other disk is MS211-005.
  MS211-005: 'BQ raw data files from BC vax' [original title]. The original is the second of two floppy disks found in folder "BQ-BC data-2000." These disks were found in an envelope wrapped in a letter from Rani E. Dalgin of Boston College (which remains in the folder). This disk contains .DAT files.
  Disks found in MS211.005.068:
  MS211-002: 'BQ Boundary.1 RC384 New Data ~65 Ss 6/20/95' [original title]. The original is a floppy disk found in folder "Boundary Q – Computer." The disk sleeve is titled "Simpson" and the disk itself is titled "Dr. Ernest Hartmann M.D. Boundary Questionnaires Boundary.1 RC: 384 New Data ~65 Ss 6/20/95." The disk contains two files, one .dat format, the other without a file type.
  MS211-003: '9/14/93 Copy of BQ Data - Bamada "RC 522" Ss 01-517 to 01-603' [original title]. The original is a floppy disk found in folder titled "New Ss 1-517 to 1-603." The folder contains a letter that gives some context for the data. The disk contains a single file, of no recognizable file type, called Boundary.1.
  MS211-007: 'Read Boundary Questionnaire Simpson' [original title]. The original is a 5¼" floppy disk found in folder titled "Boundary Q – Computer." The disk has not yet been digitized. It was found in an envelope addressed to Hartmann from some with the surname Simpson; the disk label reads "Read Boundary Questionnaire – Simpson." It has been placed in the collection documentation folder until it can be digitized and the contents further described.
  Oversized materials relating to the Boundary Questionnaire studies are housed in MS211.005.070, and related hand-drawn charts originally packed in Box 14 have been rehoused in MS211.005.004.
  Temporary processing note: Blank copies of forms and tests were weeded. Published articles found among research materials were weeded when discovered; unpublished research by other researchers was kept with the original study or subject area.
  This is a temporary description based on unprocessed materials and will need to be expanded with future processing. Material in this series has been grouped by research study or research area; an attempt was made to order studies by their start date. Because studies and periods of research overlapped, no strict chronology was possible.
  Most material of a particular study or research area was originally grouped together; some, like the Boundary Questionnaire material, was found in filing cabinets and drawers located in different parts of Hartmann's house. An attempt was made during rehousing to reintegrate materials pertaining to the same study or research area.
  For shorter research studies, Hartmann filed his research data with the publication draft currently found in Series 4: Scientific publications and drafts.
  - Data sheets BQ, 1973 -- 1989; MS211.005.031. (Box 31)
    From boxes 16, 17
  - Data sheets BA, LGV, 1972 -- 1985; MS211.005.032. (Box 32)
    From box 16
  - Long-short, 1967 -- 1969; MS211.005.033. (Box 33)
    From filing cabinet 9, drawer 3
  - Long-short sleeper study, 1967 -- 1969; MS211.005.034. (Box 34)
    From filing cabinet 9, drawer 3, and filing cabinet 9, drawer 4
  - Tryptophan study, 1983 -- 1991; MS211.005.035. (Box 35)
    From filing cabinet 16, drawer 3
  - Tryptophan study, 1983 -- 1991; MS211.005.036. (Box 36)
    From filing cabinet 16, drawer 3, and filing cabinet 16, drawer 4
  - Tryptophan study, 1966 -- 1986; MS211.005.037. (Box 37)
    From box 8
  - Tryptophan A patient files 033-069, 1900 -- 2014; MS211.005.038. (Box 38)
    From filing cabinet 14, drawer 1, and filing cabinet 14, drawer 2
  - Tryptophan A project patient 070-104, 1900 -- 2014; MS211.005.039. (Box 39)
    From filing cabinet 14, drawer 2
  - Tryptophan A patient files 105-128, 1985 -- 1988; MS211.005.040. (Box 40)
    From filing cabinet 14, drawer 2, and filing cabinet 14, drawer 3
  - Tryptophan A patient files 129-139, 1983 -- 1989; MS211.005.041. (Box 41)
    From filing cabinet 7, drawer 1, filing cabinet 14, drawer 3, and filing cabinet 14, drawer 4
  - Tryptophan NDA, notes and study, 1970 -- 1984; MS211.005.042. (Box 42)
    From filing cabinet 7, drawer 1, and filing cabinet 14, drawer 4
  - Tryptophan NDA, research, alleg, 1966 -- 1983; MS211.005.043. (Box 43)
    From filing cabinet 7, drawer 1, filing cabinet 13, drawer 1, and box 16
  - Various studies, 1970 -- 1979; MS211.005.044. (Box 44)
    From filing cabinet 6, drawer 3
  - Nightmare study, 1979 -- 1986; MS211.005.045. (Box 45)
    From filing cabinet 15, drawer 1, and filing cabinet 16, drawer 1
  - Nightmare study, 1976 -- 1980; MS211.005.046. (Box 46)
    From filing cabinet 10, drawer 3, and filing cabinet 15, drawer 1
  - Nightmare study, 1979 -- 1981; MS211.005.047. (Box 47)
    From filing cabinet 15, drawer 1, and box 16
  - NM/NT study patient files BQ Gr, 1984 -- 2002; MS211.005.048. (Box 48)
    From filing cabinet 4, drawer 1
  - NM/NT boundary group BQs, 1984 -- 1990; MS211.005.049. (Box 49)
    From filing cabinet 4, drawer 1, and filing cabinet 4, drawer 2
  - Boundary of mind correspondence, group 109-362, 1989 -- 1994; MS211.005.050. (Box 50)
    From filing cabinet 4, drawer 2, and filing cabinet 4, drawer
  - Alcohol and bruxism study, 1981 -- 1986; MS211.005.051. (Box 51)
    From filing cabinet 16, drawer 2
  - Alcohol and bruxism study, 1984 -- 1992; MS211.005.052. (Box 52)
  - Alocohol and bruxism study, grant files, 1984 -- 1985; MS211.005.053. (Box 53)
    From filing cabinet 15, drawer 3, and boxes 6 and 7
  - Vuln-schiz Judge Baker/Glueck, 1982 -- 1986; MS211.005.054. (Box 54)
    From filing cabinet 3, drawer 3
  - Vuln-schiz Judge Baker, 1944 -- 1982; MS211.005.055. (Box 55)
    From filing cabinet 10, drawer 1
  - Vuln-schiz Judge Baker, notes, 1941 -- 1987; MS211.005.056. (Box 56)
    From filing cabinet 10, drawer 1, and filing cabinet 10, drawer 3
  - Vuln-schiz Judge Baker, data and unpublished, 1975 -- 1983; MS211.005.057. (Box 57)
    From filing cabinet 10, drawer 2, and filing cabinet 10, drawer 3
  - 9-11 study, 2002 -- 2006; MS211.005.058. (Box 58)
    From filing cabinet I (2nd floor), drawer 2
  - 9-11 study, CI, 1995 -- 2006; MS211.005.059. (Box 59)
    From filing cabinet I (2nd floor), drawer 2, and filing cabinet II (2nd floor), drawer 2
  - Contextualizing Images, 1996 -- 2001; MS211.005.060. (Box 60)
    From filing cabinet II (2nd floor), drawer 2, and filing cabinet II (2nd floor), drawer 3
  - Contextualizing Images blank tests, 2001 -- 2003; MS211.005.061. (Box 61)
    From filing cabinet 5, drawer 1, filing cabinet 5, drawer 2, and filing cabinet II (2nd floor), drawer 3
  - Blank tests, MMPI, 1900 -- 2014; MS211.005.062. (Box 62)
    From filing cabinet 5, drawer 2, and filing cabinet I (2nd floor), drawer 1
  - BQ, boundary bunch data, 1985 -- 2000; MS211.005.063. (Box 63)
    From filing cabinet 1, drawer 1
  - BQ materials, 1985 -- 1996; MS211.005.064. (Box 64)
    From filing cabinet 1, drawer 1, and filing cabinet 1, drawer 2
  - BQ materials, 1985 -- 1993; MS211.005.065. (Box 65)
    From filing cabinet 1, drawer 2, and filing cabinet 1, drawer 3
  - BQ dissertations, data, consent forms, 1986 -- 1989; MS211.005.066. (Box 66)
    From filing cabinet 1, drawer 3, and filing cabinet 6, drawer 1.
  - BQ consent forms, data, score sheets, 1986 -- 1991; MS211.005.067. (Box 67)
    From filing cabinet 4, drawer 3, and filing cabinet 6, drawer 1
  - BQ shore sheets, 1988 -- 1993; MS211.005.068. (Box 68)
    From filing cabinet 4, drawer 3, and box 2
  - BQ data and various studies, 1968 -- 1986; MS211.005.069. (Box 69)
    From filing cabinet 13, drawer 1, filing cabinet 15, drawer 1, and box 2
  - Oversize datasheets BQ & LDT, 1979 -- 1980; MS211.005.070. (Box 70)
    From filing cabinet 1, drawer 3, and box 12
  - BQ data and scoresheets, 1989 -- 1999; MS211.005.071. (Box 71)
    From box 1 and box 17
- Early 20th century Austrian and German psychoanalytic literature and other books, 1913 -- 1940; MS211.006; 14.4 Linear Feet
  This is a temporary description based on unprocessed materials and will need to be expanded with future processing. This series includes early Austrian and German psychoanalytic journals (Imago, Allgemeine Auml;rtzliche Zeitschrift fuuml;r Psychotherapie, Zentralblatt fuuml;r Psychotherapie, and Internationale Zeitschrift fuuml;r Psychoanalyse) and books from 1902 to the 1950's originally owned by members of the Hartmann family. Some of the journals have small notations on the covers or on specific articles. Journals are entirely in German and contain work by prominent psychoanalysts, including Freud, Heinz Hartmann and possibly Dora Hartmann. The books range from psychoanalytic texts, education, and social science, and literature and are primarily in German but one is in French.
  Journals are arranged by publication and then by date. Books are not yet arranged.
  - Professional literature, Internationale Zeitschrift f r Psychoanalyse., 1922 -- 1931; MS211.006.072 (Box 72)
    A series of Internationale Zeitschrift fur Psychoanalyse.The material is in German. The years 1923-1924 as well as Volume 1 from the the 1931 edition are missing.
  - Professional literature, Internationale Zeitschrift f r Psychoanalyse and Allgemeine &#196rtzliche Zeitschrift f r Psychotherapie und Psychische Hygiene, 1928 -- 1940; MS211.006.073 (Box 73)
    Missing volumes 1and 2 from 1932, volume 1 from 1935, and volume 4 from 1939 in Internationale Zeitschrift fur Psychoanalyse.
    magazine (periodical)
  - Professional Literature, Allgemeine Ärtzliche Zeitschrift für Psychotherapie und Psychische Hygiene, Zentralblatt für Psychotherapie, and Imago., 1913 -- 1933; MS211.006.074 (Box 74)
    Allgemeine Ärtzliche Zeitschrift für Psychotherapie und Psychische Hygiene is missing the first volume in 1929. Allgemeine Ärtzliche Zeitschrift für Psychotherapie und Psychische Hygiene changed names to Zentralblatt für Psychotherapie. Imago's bulk dates are 1931-1933 and there are large gaps series.
  - Professional literature, Imago, 1930 -- 1937; MS211.006.075 (Box 75)
  - Bound journals 1923-1926, remnant folders, and boxed books., MS211.006.092 (Box 92)
    The folders in Box 92 contain loose pages or sections of volumes and journals.
    The unboxed books:
    .Zentralblatt für die Gesamte Neurologie und Psychiatrie– vols. 41-44, 1925-1926
    Internationale Zeitschrift für Psychologie – vols. 9-10, 1923-1924
    Box 1:
    Entwicklung und Glückseligkeit: Ethische Essays - B. Carneri, 1886
    Archiv für die gesamte Psychologie. vol.9, heft 1, 1907
    Revue Francaise de Psychanalyse, Nov. 1, 1951
    Bewusstsein Als Verhangnis
    Schicksal und Neurose, 1931
    Hartmann, Ernest, 1934-; Hartmann, Heinz, 1894-1970; Hartmann, Dora, 1902-1974
  - Boxed books, some autographed., MS211.006.093 (Box 93)
    Box 4
    Zur Analyse der Gedachtnistatigkeit und des Vorstellungsverlaufes – 1924
    Archiv für die gesamte Psychologie.vol. 9, heft 4, 1907
    Versuch einer Entwicklungsgeschichte der Libido – Abraham, 1924
    Mutterrechtliche Familie und Odipus-Komplex – Malinowski, 1924
    Ein Experimenteller Beitrag zur Erforschung des Unterbewussten – Martin, 1915
    Handbuch der Psychiatrie – Aschaffenburg, 1912
    Psychoanalyse und seelische Wirklichkeit – Maag, 1930
    Medizinische Anthropologie – Schwarz, 1929
    Allgemeine Neurosenlehre – Nunberg, 1932
    Psyche – Band 1, Folge 1, 1947
    Spiritismus und Geistesstorung – Henneberg, 1902
    Uber den Willen – Narziss Ach, 1910
    Uber den Willensakt: Eine Replik – Narziss Ach, 1911
    Das Unbewusste – Levine, 1926
    Das Naturgesetz – Bauch, 1924 (from series Wissenschaftliche Grundfragen)
    Deutsche Geschichte – Sonderdruck – Band VIII – erste Halste – Lamprecht, ~1906
    Deutsche Geschichte – Sonderdruck – Band I – Vierte Auflage – Lamprecht, ~1906
    Grundlinien der Psychoanalyse – Haeberlin, 1927
    Rede Uber Hofmannsthal – Rudolf Borchardt,1918
    Box 13 – autographed/dedicated
    Die Psychische Impotenz des Mannes – Bergler, 1937
    Uber Psychoanalyse – Allers, 1922
    Kritik der Reinen Erfahrung – 2nd part – Avenarius, 1908
    Die Storungen der Lautspreche bei Temporallappenlasionen – Bonvicini, 1929
    Hartmann, Heinz, 1894-1970; Hartmann, Ernest, 1934-; Hartmann, Dora, 1902-1974
  - Boxed books, some autographed., MS211.006.094 (Box 94)
    Box 3
    Unidentified science book, German
    Zirkus – Paul Eipper, 1930
    Psychogenese und Psychotherapie Korperlicher Symptome – Oswald Schwarz, 1925
    Box 8 – Dora Hartmann
    Der Weisse Heiland – Hauptmann, 1920
    Freuds Tragischer Komplex – Maylan, 1929
    Psychologie – Adolf Stohr, 1917
    Box 12 – autographed
    Clinique Psychanalytique – Laforgue, 1934-1936
    Die Bedeutung der Kindheitseindrucke fur das werden des Charakters und der
    Gesamtpersonlichkeit – Beau, 1930
    Siegfried Kapper – Donath, 1934
    Schöpferische Entwicklung – Henri Bergson, 1912
  - Boxed books, MS211.006.095 (Box 95)
    Box 2
    Wesen und Vorgang der Suggestion
    Handbuch der Psychiatrie, Aschaffenburg, ed.
    Gemeinschaftsbild und Gemeinschaftskrafte, Stefan Georges
    Der Begriff des Typus, 1933
    Die Entwicklung des menschlichen Geistes
    Das Verhältnis der Psychoanalyse zu Ethik, Religion und Seelsorge – 1st ed.
    Homosexualität und Recht – Placzek, 1925
    Die Gastpflege der Ameisen – Wasmann, 1920
    Box 6 – possibly Ludo Moritz Hartmann
    Die Philosophie Herakleitos des Dunklen von Ephesos, vol. 1, 1858
    Die Philosophie Herakleitos des Dunklen von Ephesos, vol. 2, 1858
    Der Anfang: Zeitschrift der Jugend, Juni 1914
    Unidentified portion of book
    Box 7 – possibly Ludo Moritz Hartmann
    Talleyrand – Napoleon – Stendhal – Grabbe by Bergler, 1935 (signed by author)
    Aus nachgelassenen Schriften eines Frühvollendeten – Otto Braun, 1920
    Box 11
    Soziologie – Simmel, 1908
    Bericht uber den V. Kongress fur experimentelle Psychologie – Schumann, 1912
    Archiv für die gesamte Psychologie, vol. 9, heft 2/3, 1907
  - Bilder-Lexikon [der Erotik]: Kulturgeschichte (1928), Ergänzungsband zum Bilder-Lexikon [der Erotik] (1931), and other boxed books, MS211.006.096; Institut für Sexualforschung (Vienna, Austria) (Box 96)
    Container has following container list:
    Bilder-Lexikon – 2 boxes
    Full title: Bilder-Lexikon [der Erotik]: ein Nachschlagewerk für die Begriffe und Erscheinungen auf dem Gebiete der Kulturgeschichte, Sittengeschichte, Folklore, Ethnographie, des Kult- und Mysterienwesens, Gesellschaftslebens, der Chronique scandaleuse, für Zeitdokumente und Biographien: ein Sammelwerk sittengeschichtlicher Bilddokumente aller Völker und Zeiten. First volume. Front cover and spine detached, leather binding deteriorating, some staining.
    Full title: Ergänzungsband zum Bilder-Lexikon: Kulturgeschichte - Literatur und Kunst - Sexualwissenschaft. Text- und Bildnachträge zum Nachschlagwerk für alle Gebiete medizinischer, juridischer, soziologischer, literarischhistorischer, kunstgeschichtlicher und kulturwissenschaftlicher Sexualforschung. Supplement to first volume. Cover boards missing, title pages partially destroyed or missing, stained, and damaged.
    Other boxed books seem to have belonged to Dora Karplus Hartmann.
    Box 9 – Dora Karplus Hartmann
    Hyperion – Holderlin, 1922
    Judith – Hebbel
    Diagnostik und Therapie der Kinderkrankheiten – Lust, 1929
    Statistisches Praktikum für Psychologen und Lehrer
- Employment files, 1980 -- 2009; MS211.007; 1 Volumes
  This is a temporary description based on unprocessed materials and will need to be expanded with future processing. This series contains the various professional and work-related documents of Ernest L. Hartmann. These materials include CV's, medical licenses and certifications, contracts, insurance documents, lease agreements, awards, booklets, and some photos ranging from 1980-2009. This series also contains his professional headshots from 1980 to 1990 and several iterations of his professional curriculum vitae. Intermixed in this series is correspondence on research projects and personal projects.
  Hartmann, as a prescribing psychiatrist, was required to maintain various certifications and licenses. The bulk of the material is related to renewal of his provider status with various insurance companies and renewal of medical malpractice insurance and certifications.
  This is a proposed idea for arrangement based on unprocessed materials. This series is in rough chronological order with CV materials located in the front and can be refined during additional processing.
  - Benefits, CV, records, 1980 -- 2009; MS211.007.076. (Box 76)
    From filing cabinet I (2nd floor), drawer 4
- Unsorted boxes, 1900 -- 2014; MS211.008; 1 Volumes
  This is a temporary description based on unprocessed materials and will need to be expanded with future processing. This series consists of material that was too varied to be assigned to a single series during rehousing. Material was kept together as found, contextual labels were kept (e.g. where materials were found in Ernest Hartmann's house or filing cabinets) where available. Future processing will involve assigning material into various series or determining the relationship of the materials in their existing order.
  Contents include ephemera, official documents and certifications, research, data, publications and manuscripts, photographs, and personal and professional correspondence. Future processers should be careful not to attempt to separate professional from personal correspondence, as many professional colleagues were also family friends and because this is how Ernest Hartmann filed his correspondence for the overwhelming part (keeping professional and personal correspondence together).
  Extensive personal and family material exists in Series 8: Unsorted boxes. MS211.008.080 contains writings by Eva Neumann and files related to her and Hartmann's 1999 divorce. MS211.008.082 contains stationery and personal correspondence. MS211.008.083 contains Hartmann's creative writing, official documents from Heinz and Dora Hartmann's families, and paperwork relating to their deaths. MS211.008.087 contains personal correspondence and photos from a 1985 reunion.
  Two CDs found in this series have been digitized. The physical location of the disks at the time of rehousing have been flagged, i.e. markers and separations sheets have been added to the physical files.
  Disks in MS211.008.078:
  MS211-001: 'Kelly Bulkely SD1 3: 1-525' [original title]. Originally the CD was found unfoldered between an untitled folder and another called "KB," all of which were within a larger folder called "CI [illegible] 99." The disk contains in a single folder called "Sleep and Dream Interviews," with 525 .txt files related to the Contextualizing Images study (and possibly the 9/11 study); files were compiled by Kelly Bulkely, colleague of Hartmann.
  MS211-006: 'BQ_Data_Hartman_010301_1232' [original title]. The CD labeled "Hartman" was found in a folder labeled "BQ – BC-BQ All Data (Disc) CD." When migrating the files from the CD computer read the title of the CD as "010301-1232" which contained 24 files, mostly .sas and .SPS files readable by SPSS and SAS, all related to the Boundary Questionnaire. The CD also contains a Readme.doc created by the original researcher which explains the context of the files and how to open them.
  This is a temporary description based on unprocessed materials and will need to be expanded with future processing. These containers are in no order.
  - CI, publications, ASD, SRF unsorted, 1900 -- 2014; MS211.008.078. (Box 78)
    From filing cabinet I (2nd floor), drawer 1
  - Recent talks, papers, 1900 -- 2014; MS211.008.079. (Box 79)
    From filing cabinet II (2nd floor), drawer 4
  - Postcards, cards, and professional correspondence, 1900 -- 2014; MS211.008.080. (Box 80)
    From boxes 12, 18
  - BQ, Tryptophan, applications, grants, etc., 1988 -- 2000; MS211.008.081. (Box 81)
    From box 17
  - Personal files, professional files, 1997 -- 2005; MS211.008.082. (Box 82)
    From filing cabinet 9, drawer 2, and boxes 7, 19, and 20
  - Poetry, prose, family documents, 1900 -- 2014; MS211.008.083. (Box 83)
    From boxes 18, 19
  - Recent talks, papers, grants, 1900 -- 2014; MS211.008.084. (Box 84)
    From box 16, filing cabinet II (2nd floor), drawer 4, and filing cabinet III (2nd floor), drawer 4
  - Studies, patient files, notebooks, 1960 -- 1988; MS211.008.085. (Box 85)
    From boxes 12, 16
  - Data, studies, corresondence, 1900 -- 2014; MS211.008.086. (Box 86)
    From box 13
  - Publications, notebooks, reviews, 1985 -- 2010; MS211.008.087. (Box 87)
  - Publications, research, reviews of other, 1900 -- 2014; MS211.008.088. (Box 88)
    From filing cabinet III (2nd floor), drawer 2, and filing cabinet III (2nd floor), drawer 3
  - A-Z unpublished materials, thesis, 1900 -- 2014; MS211.008.089. (Box 89)
    From filing cabinet 2, drawer 3, and filing cabinet 2, drawer 4
  - Associated research, publications, drafts, 1964 -- 1997; MS211.008.090. (Box 90)
    From boxes 1, 7, and 10
  - Publications, correspondence, talks, 1900 -- 2014; MS211.008.091. (Box 91)
    From filing cabinet 8, drawer 3
- Audio tapes, 1977 -- 1983; MS211.009; 3.6 Linear Feet
  This is a temporary description based on unprocessed materials and will need to be expanded with future processing. This series contains eleven audio cassette albums (129 tapes) ranging from 1977-1983; the contents of the tapes range from talks given by Hartmann to interviews and nightmare research, Thematic Appreciation Tests (TATs), Rorschach tests, and dream reports. Each album holds twelve cassette tapes except for one double album containing twenty-four tapes. Four of the albums are missing items. Some of the albums contain indexes of the materials and most of the tapes are labeled with the subject and frequently a rough date.
  All albums are currently in one box in no specific order.
  - Audio tapes interviews and talks, 1977 -- 1983; MS211.009.077 (Box 77)
    This box contains eleven audio cassette albums (129 tapes) ranging from 1977-1983. The contents of the tapes range from talks given by Hartmann to interviews and nightmare research, Thematic Appreciation Tests (TATs), Rorschach tests, and dream reports.
    audiocassettes
- Digital files, 1993 -- 2007; MS211.010; 6 Digital Object(s)
  - Kelly Bulkely SD1 3: 1-525, 2007; MS211-001
    Original location was a CD found unfoldered between an untitled folder and another called "KB," all of which were part of a larger folder called "CI [illegible] 99." Files are contained in a single folder called "Sleep and Dream Interviews," which contains 525 .TXT files related to the Contextualizing Images study (and possibly the 9/11 study) compiled by Kelly Bulkely, colleague of Hartmann. From box MS211.008.078, Series 8: Unsorted boxes.
  - BQ Boundary.1 RC384 New Data ~65 Ss 6/20/95, 1995-06-20; MS211-002
    Original is a floppy disk found in folder "Boundary Q – Computer." The disk sleeve reads "Simpson" and the disk reads "Dr. Ernest Hartmann M.D. Boundary Questionnaires Boundary.1 RC: 384 New Data ~65 Ss 6/20/95." The disk contains two files, one .dat format, the other without a file type. From box MS211.005.068 of Series 5: Research and Data.